australiagsm.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy | AustraliaGSMAustraliaGSM

AustraliaGSM.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy while providing our Australian Immigration Online Application Services. We encourage you to periodically review this statement as it may change from time to time at our sole discretion. This Privacy Policy statement explains the personal information gathering and use practices of the AustraliaGSM Organization. Questions concerning your personal information should be directed to our Privacy Officer by e-mail at [privacy@AustraliaGSM.com](mailto:privacy@AustralianVisaExpert.com).

All capitalized terms used herein shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the [Terms of Use](http://www.australiagsm.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use") .

**If you do not WISH THAT WE COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM YOU, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE US WITH SUCH INFORMATION.   FURTHERMORE, IF YOU DO NOT agree to BE BOUND by this policy and/or the terms of use and/or or any future terms, you may not use the WEBSITE OR THE  Services.**

**Information Collected**

AustraliaGSM.com collects personal identifiable information about you in connection with your use of the Website the Services and throughout the duration of such use, including:

  * Name
  * Age
  * Gender
  * Address
  * Phone and/or mobile numbers
  * Country
  * Zip code
  * Email
  * IP address and browser information;
  * Photos uploaded by you
  * Credit card numbers
  * Market research data such as customer usage patterns;

AustraliaGSM.com further collects personal identifiable information about you in the context of the Services offered on the Website or in connection therewith such as the information so collected in the applications filled out by you online and/or through the assistance of the AustraliaGSM representatives.

In addition to providing the foregoing to us, if you chose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

All such data described above shall be referred to herein as your “ **Personal Data** ”.

Please be advised that you are not under any legal obligation to provide us with any information including any Personal Data, and providing such information is entirely subject to your sole discretion and consent.

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

We use your Personal Data for the purposes of providing the Services, including, without limitation, generating and sending you feedback on your applications as well as submitting your application to the relevant Australian agency in charge of administering the relevant immigration program.

In addition we will use your Personal Data for legitimate business operational and marketing purposes, which may include:

  * Enhancing our customer service
  * Processing orders and inquiries
  * Improving our website and services
  * Resolving disputes, collecting fees, and troubleshooting problems.
  * Conducting market research surveys.
  * Occasionally offering current subscribers the chance to participate in contests or surveys.
  * Providing you with information about products and services we offer, inter alia, through direct mailing. **You may stop the delivery of marketing emails by following the instructions accompanying a particular communication or by contacting us at**[privacy **@** AustraliaGSM.com](mailto:privacy@CanadianVisaExpert.com).

For the aforesaid purposes we disclose Personal Data, including without limitation information gathered by means of Cookies (see below) to those of our employees and our service providers who: (a) need to know this information in order to process it on our behalf, or to provide services offered through or relating to the Website; and (b) have agreed not to disclose it to others. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Data to those service providers. We shall not sell or make available the Personal Data to anyone other than to our employees and service providers as described herein. We may however also disclose your Personal Data to third parties (a) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process (including any court order) or governmental request, (b) to perform certain administrative functions consistent with our Privacy Policy on our behalf, (c) to protect the safety of our employees and our property, and (d) and in connection with enforcement of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

AustraliaGSM may share information about users with business partners, sponsors and other third parties. We provide this information in aggregate form so that no individual user is identified.

By accepting these terms you consent to AustraliaGSM.com and/or other third parties as aforesaid sending messages to you via email regarding products, new services, improvements, notice of scheduled services, etc. **If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from us and/or from third-party companies,** you may opt-out of receiving this information by sending us an  **e-mail to[privacy@AustraliaGSM.com](mailto:privacy@AustralianVisaExpert.com)**. We will take appropriate steps to fulfill your request within reasonable time; however, it may take a few days or longer to process your request during which you may still receive marketing communications from us. We reserve the right to send you non-marketing notice about your account, even if you opt-out of all email notifications.

If you decide to terminate your account with us, you may do so by sending us an email to [csr@australiagsm.com](mailto:csr@australiagsm.com) specifying your request and providing us with your Username and email address with which you registered. If you terminate your account, your profile will be removed from the Site, however, deletion may not be immediate and we may continue keeping your personal information in our records for audits and other administrative purposes.

**Payment Collection Information**

When purchasing the Services and/or any other product via the Website using a credit card, you will be asked to submit data such as the credit card number and details. AustraliaGSM.com is hosted on a secure server and uses the most updated information security technology, whose purpose is to protect your credit card details during the transmission of data stored on the servers. This SSL technology (‘Secure Sockets Layers’), secures billions of dollars’ worth of transactions over the Internet. AustraliaGSM.com uses a mediator such as PayPal and GiroPay for the purpose of providing alternative payment solutions.

**Children’s privacy**

This Site is intended for users over the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information online from, or market online to, children under 18.  If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

**Security  ** **Policy**

Subject to your undertakings to protect the confidentiality of your username and password as further described in the Terms of Use, AustraliaGSM.com has appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users’ Personal Data is protected against unauthorized access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss. Although we make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. We have adopted security tools and procedures that limit access to private and personal information as well as locates and prevents access from unauthorized users. While our security measures are consistent with the industry standards and we have not been served with any claims regarding the penetrability of our security system _,_  there is some risk that thieves could find a way to thwart our security systems.

We utilize ‘Cookies’ on your computer in order to simplify the user’s experience. You can set your browser preferences to a ‘cookie’ rejecting mode, but be advised that the service may not function properly. AustraliaGSM.com data is stored behind ‘Firewalls’ so as to prevent loss, changing or misuse of information under our control.

AustraliaGSM.com includes links to different sites. Please note that when ‘clicking’ any of these links, your computer will be directed to another separate website. We advise that you read the Privacy Protection Notice on these sites, since theirs may differ from ours.

**International Transfer**

It may be necessary to transfer your Personal Data internationally to recipients located outside your territory either within the AustraliaGSM’s group or to third party service providers. Please be assured that we take all reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected.

**Access to Data and Contact Info**

You may request a copy or send a correction of the personal information we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer at [privacy@AustraliaGSM.com](mailto:privacy@AustraliaGSM.com) or by contacting our customer support at [csr@australiagsm.com](mailto:csr@australiagsm.com).

**Changes to this Policy**

Periodically, we may make changes to this privacy policy statement or the manner of use of your personal information to reflect any changes to our privacy practices. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a prominent notice on our Website.  In any event you should review our Privacy Policy prior to each use of the Service, particularly each time before you submit your Personal Data through the Service, so you could be informed of any changes in our privacy practices. At all times, the most current version of our privacy policy will supersede any other versions of our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website will constitute your consent to any such changes in the Privacy Policy except where otherwise required by applicable law.
